Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Canter Achenbaum Associates (Includes Canter Achenbaum Heekin), 1960-2004 and undated
  - Account Files
    - PCA International Acquisition Company
      - Prepaid package audit, 1984 (Box CA31)
      - Promotion, 1985-1986 (Box CA32)
      - Proofs Plus, 1985 (Box CA32)
      - Stock and shareholder information, 1986 (Box CA32)
      - Study of the Consumer Portrait Market, 1984 (Box CA32)
    - Philip Morris
      - Assessment of Merit's Current Market Situation, 1985 (Box CA32)
      - Bill Campbell meeting, 1991 (Box CA32)
      - Branding, undated (Box CA32)
      - Consumer Evaluations of Merit Cigarettes, 1979 (Box CA32)
      - Consumer Testing of Merit Cigarettes, undated (Box CA32)
      - Evaluating the Effectiveness of Price-Off Promotions in the Cigarette Market, 1983 (Box CA32)
      - Maxwell consumer report, 1989 (Box CA32)
      - Merit Advertising Guidelines, 1986 (Box CA32)
      - National Taste Test--Triumph vs. Competitors, undated (Box CA32)
      - Philip Morris Magazine Marketing Strategy Recommendations, 1988 (Box CA32)
      - Pricing in the Cigarette Market, 1991 (Box CA32)
      - Reassessment of Merit's Market Situation, 1987 (Box CA33)
      - Remarks by Alvin Achenbaum, 1975 (Box CA33)
    - Procter & Gamble
      - P&G vs. Nabisco cookie case, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box CA33)
    - Quaker Oats
      - Agency compensation studies, 1976 (Box CA33)
    - R.R. Donnelley/CDN (Classified Directories Network)
      - Advantages and Disadvantages of a Separately Printed and Distributed Color Pages Book, 1978 (Box CA33)
      - Color Pages
        - Compendium of Six Analyses, undated (Box CA33)
        - Description and Positioning, 1977 (Box CA33)
        - Presentation, 1977 (Box CA33)
        - Pricing, 1977 (Box CA33)
        - Test research outline, undated (Box CA33)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box CA33)
      - Naming, Positioning and Estimating Market Potential, 1978 (Box CA34)
      - Outline and task analysis, undated (Box CA34)
      - Positioning, undated (Box CA34)
      - Solving CDN's Problems while Substantially Increasing Profitability, undated (Box CA34)
      - Target advertisers, 1978 (Box CA34)
    - S.C. Johnson
      - Assessment of In-House Media Function, 1987 (Box CA34)
    - Scott Paper
      - Advertising Agency Performance Incentive Bonus System, 1989 (Box CA34)
    - Seagram
      - Assessment of Advertising Agency Services from a Financial and Policy Perspective, 1985 (Box CA34)
    - Seiko
      - Compensation assessment, 1987, (2 folders) (Box CA34)
    - Sentry Insurance
      - Consumer Oriented Life Insurance, 1976 (Box CA34)
      - Discussion of New Insurance Distribution Systems, 1978 (Box CA34)
      - Outline of Presentation of Retail Insurance System (RIS) Concept, 1978 (Box CA34)
      - Research proposal, 1979 (Box CA34)
      - Situation Analysis of Consumer Oriented Life Insurance, 1976 (Box CA34)
      - Umbrella Hazard Insurance, 1976 (Box CA34)
      - Work Session on Proposed Retail Insurance System, 1978 (Box CA34)
    - Standard Brands
      - Maximizing Advertising Agency Productivity, 1978 (Box CA35)
    - Steuben Glass
      - Agency selection, 1989 (Box CA35)
    - Subaru
      - Agency agreement, 1989 (Box CA35)
      - Agency compensation review, 1989 (Box CA35)
      - Compensation, 1989 and undated (Box CA35)
      - Study of compensation arrangement, 1989 (Box CA35)
    - Toyota
      - 1980 Model Year Dynamic Study, 1981 (Box CA35)
      - 1981 Annual Study Top Line Data, 1981 (Box CA36)
      - Agency compensation, 1975 and undated (Box CA36)
      - Agency performance review, 1980, 1986 (Box CA36)
      - Agency search, 1980-1981 (Box CA36)
      - Agency search--Operation Babe Ruth, 1975 and undated (Box CA36)
      - Agency search--Project America, undated (Box CA36)
      - Annual Commission Review, 1983-1986 (Box CA36)
      - Assessment of Current Compensation Arrangement, 1983, 1987, (1 of 2 folders) (Box CA36)
      - Assessment of Current Compensation Arrangement, 1983, 1987, (2 of 2 folders) (Box CA37)
      - Consumer's View of the Automobile Market, 1979-1981 (Box CA37)
      - Consumer's View of the Automobile Market, 1981, (2 folders) (Box CA38)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1980-1989 (Box CA38)
      - Dynamic Research of the U.S. New Car Market, 1980 (Box CA38)
      - Forecast of new car sales, 1976 (Box CA38)
      - Fourth Advertising Agency Performance Review, 1988 (Box CA38)
      - Market Potential Analysis, 1976 (Box CA38)
      - Media Effectiveness Test, 1981 (Box CA38)
      - New Method for Calculating Toyota Planning Potentials, 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box CA39)
      - Precise Market Potentials for Geographically Allocating Marketing Efforts, 1975 (Box CA39)
      - Strategic plan, 1974 (Box CA39)
      - Superweek Research Project, 1979 (Box CA39)
      - Technical Appendix, 1979-1980, (3 folders) (Box CA39)
      - Third Advertising Agency Performance Review, 1986 (Box CA40)
      - Toyota Market Potential Analysis, 1975 (Box CA40)
    - TV Guide
      - Agency compensation review, 1985 (Box CA40)
      - Assessment of compensation arrangement, 1985 (Box CA40)
      - Pro forma agreement, 1985 (Box CA40)
      - Proposed compensation arrangement, 1985 (Box CA40)
      - Strategic plan, 1986 (Box CA40)
    - Uncle Ben's
      - Agency compensation review, 1989 (Box CA40)
      - Assessment of Compensation Arrangement with Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1989, (3 folders) (Box CA40)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box CA41)
      - Compensation presentation, 1989 (Box CA41)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1989 (Box CA41)
    - Veryfine
      - Agency compensation arrangement, undated (Box CA41)
    - Wells Rich Greene
      - Acquiring Other Advertising Agencies, 1976 (Box CA41)
    - Western Union
      - Marketing position paper on the telegram business, 1985 (Box CA41)
    - Wisconsin Bell
      - Proposed Agency Compensation Arrangement, 1989 (Box CA41)
    - XYZ Company
      - A Short and Sweet Media Study Concerning Your Bottom Line, 1989 (Box CA41)
  - General Files
    - Advertising Media--They're Still a Bargain, 1976 (Box CA41)
    - Agency Search and Selection
      - Agency brief, undated (Box CA41)
      - Agency performance measures, 1988-1991 (Box CA41)
      - Agency selection samples, undated (Box CA41)
      - Evaluation criteria, undated (Box CA41)
      - Meetings book template, undated (Box CA41)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box CA41)
      - Proposals and contracts, 1988-1989 (Box CA41)
      - Questions, 1989 (Box CA41)
      - Releases, undated (Box CA41)
      - Screening/first meetings, 1988 and undated (Box CA42)
      - Search decisions, 1987-1988 (Box CA42)
      - Termination and transition, undated (Box CA42)
    - AMA marketing panel, 1989 (Box CA42)
    - AMA New Products Conference, 1988 (Box CA42)
    - ANA workshop, 1985 (Box CA42)
    - Brand management, 1988-1989 and undated (Box CA42)
    - Branding proposal, undated (Box CA42)
    - Business of Acquiring New Business, undated (Box CA42)
    - CAH/Appraiser, undated (Box CA42)
    - Cardinal Sins of Agency Management, 1987-1993 (Box CA42)
    - Chronological Memos, 1989 Feb.-Nov., (4 folders) (Box CA42)
    - Chronological Memos, 1988 Mar.=1989 Jan., (6 folders) (Box CA43)
    - Chronological Memos, 1987 Sept.-1988 Feb., (4 folders) (Box CA44)
    - Clippings, 1972-1992 (Box CA44)
    - Compensation
      - Advertising Agency Compensation, undated (Box CA44)
      - Agency contracts, 1987-1994 (Box CA44)
      - Agency reviews, 1975-1988 (Box CA44)
      - Assessment, 1986-1989 (Box CA45)
      - Break-out session remarks, undated (Box CA45)
      - Canter Achenbaum and Its Role in Advertising Agency Compensation, undated (Box CA45)
      - Clients and references, 1988-1989 (Box CA45)
      - Clippings, 1988 (Box CA45)
      - Compensation Philosophy: The Client View (by Alvin Achenbaum), undated (Box CA45)
      - Criteria for a Desirable Compensation System, undated (Box CA45)
      - Definitions, 1989 (Box CA45)
      - Issues to be addressed, undated (Box CA45)
      - Miscellaneous, 1989 and undated (Box CA45)
      - Monitoring the Agreement, 1988-1989 (Box CA45)
      - Princip-le versus Princip-al (by Richard Lessler), 1989 (Box CA45)
      - Traditional Compensation Structures: How Do You Make a Great Agreement (Alvin Achenbaum), 1997 (Box CA45)
      - Variable fee schedules, undated (Box CA45)
      - Why Use an Outside Counsel? Undated (Box CA45)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1963-1992 (Box CA45)
    - Effective Exposure in Media Planning, undated (Box CA45)
    - Growth Group joint venture, undated (Box CA45)
    - Institute for Advertising Management--Account Management Training Program, 1985-1987 (Box CA45)
    - MarketFit system, 1977 (Box CA46)
    - Marketing audit service, undated (Box CA46)
    - Marketing Matters (newsletter), 1983 (Box CA46)
    - Marketing plan presentation, undated (Box CA46)
    - Marketing planning seminar, undated, (2 folders) (Box CA46)
    - Marketing planning situation analysis manual, undated (Box CA46)
    - Marketing strategy, 1982 (Box CA46)
    - New Entry Possibilities in the Deodorant Market, circa 1975 (Box CA46)
    - New market entries, undated (Box CA46)
    - New product development, 1985-1988, (1 of 2 folders) (Box CA46)
    - New product development, 1985-1988, (2 of 2 folders) (Box CA47)
    - New Service Opportunity, 1978 (Box CA47)
    - Our objectives, undated (Box CA47)
    - Presentation, 1981 (Box CA47)
    - Presentation to Barry Goad: Retail Market in the USA, 1990, (2 folders) (Box CA47)
    - Product evaluation for Milk Mate, 1976 (Box CA47)
    - Proprietary Association seminar, 1983 (Box CA47)
    - Scenario--Diet Soft Drink Market Next 18 Months, 1979 (Box CA47)
    - Seminar on new market entries, 1975 (Box CA47)
    - Seminar on the management of marketing planning, undated (Box CA47)
    - Service and Service Warranties, 1987 (Box CA48)
    - Simupac
      - A Simulation-Based Analytic System for Evaluating Alternative Market Communications, undated (Box CA48)
      - Carter-Wallace notes, 1976 (Box CA48)
      - David Beaumont & Co., 1975 (Box CA48)
      - Miscellaneous research firms, 1975-1976 and undated (Box CA48)
      - Presentations, 1975-1979, (6 folders) (Box CA48)
      - Representative project structure, 1979 (Box CA48)
      - Sales promotion, 1976 (Box CA49)
      - Technical specifications, 1977 (Box CA49)
      - Trial runs, 1977-1979 (Box CA49)
    - Stanley Canter retirement, 1989 (Box CA49)
    - Study of the Demand for Network Television Time, vol. 1, undated (Box CA49)
    - Symposium on reach and frequency, 1972-1987 (Box CA49)
    - Task force marketing, 1977 (Box CA49)
    - Testimonial letters, 1985-1989 (Box CA49)
    - Total Marketing Communications Planning and Implementation, 1988 (Box CA49)
    - Triad marketing service, 1977 (Box CA49)
    - Yankelovich Partners, Charitable organization study, 1994, (3 folders) (Box CA49)
- Grey Advertising, 1955-1974 and undated
  - Account Files
    - Automobiles Renault
      - Consumer Study of the Canadian Compact Car Market, 1970 (Box GR1)
    - Block Drug
      - Block validation study, undated, (2 folders) (Box GR1)
      - Comparison of Five Denture Studies--England, Australia, France, Canada, United States, 1966 (Box GR1)
      - Definition of Denture Wearer Potential, 1965 (Box GR1)
      - Denture Wearer Survey, 1971, (4 folders) (Box GR1)
      - Denture Wearer Survey, undated (Box GR2)
      - Discussion of Copy Testing and Its Effectiveness, 1965 (Box GR2)
      - Effectiveness of Dentu-Crème Couponing/Sampling Program, 1965 (Box GR2)
      - Effectiveness of Dentu-Crème Lipstick Demo Commercial, 1967 (Box GR2)
      - Effectiveness of Polident Gardener Commercial, 1964 (Box GR2)
      - Effectiveness of Polident Golfer Commercial, 1965 (Box GR2)
      - Effectiveness of Polident Take Years Off Ad, 1964 (Box GR2)
      - Fact Book on the Market for Special Denture Cleansers, 1965 (Box GR2)
      - Fact Book on the Market for Denture Adhesives, 1966 (Box GR2)
      - Limited Buying Incentive Study for Poli-Grip for Market Expansion, 1967 (Box GR2)
      - Product Test of Five Denture Cleansers, 1965-1967, (2 folders) (Box GR2)
      - Review and Evaluation of Block Copy Testing Program, 1969 (Box GR2)
      - Review of Block Copy Research Tests 1963-1966, 1967 (Box GR3)
      - Special Cleanser Sales Potential Index, 1967 (Box GR3)
      - Survey of Denture Wearers, 1965, (6 folders) (Box GR3)
      - Survey of Denture Wearers in Canada, 1965-1966, (3 folders) (Box GR4)
      - Test of Three Polident Promotions, 1960 (Box GR4)
    - Bristol Myers
      - Background Analysis of the Ethical Drug Market, 1970 (Box GR4)
      - Background--Health industry, 1973 (Box GR4)
      - Buying Incentive Study of the Analgesic Market, 1966 (Box GR4)
      - Case for Advertising, undated (Box GR4)
      - Checkerboard test design, 1964 (Box GR4)
      - Commercial Testing Attitude Scale Development Study, 1964 (Box GR4)
      - Comparison of the Effectiveness of Two Bufferin Commercials, 1967 (Box GR4)
      - Conclusions and Implications for Market Target/Buying Incentive Study of the Analgesic Market, 1966 (Box GR4)
      - Effectiveness of Bufferin Breakthrough Commercial, 1967 (Box GR5)
      - Effectiveness of Bufferin Mogubgub Commercial, 1967 (Box GR5)
      - Effectiveness of Score Hair Cream Commercials, 1965 (Box GR5)
      - Effectiveness of Score Hair Cream Hands Commercial, 1964 (Box GR5)
      - Experiment with Alternative Copy Testing Exposure Methods, 1965 (Box GR5)
      - Experimental Study of Commercial Pre-Testing Exposure Methods, 1964 (Box GR5)
      - Five New Analgesic Product Concepts, 1967 (Box GR5)
      - Five New Brand Concepts for the Analgesic Market, 1967 (Box GR5)
      - Market analysis, undated, (2 folders) (Box GR5)
      - Position paper on copy testing criteria, 1964 (Box GR5)
      - Score Hands Commercial Diagnostic Study, 1964 (Box GR5)
      - Study of the National Deodorant Market, 1965 (Box GR6)
      - Working Document for Use in the Development of New Product Ideas in the Analgesic Market, 1966 (Box GR6)
    - BVD
      - Buying Incentive Study, 1968 (Box GR6)
    - Calvert
      - Market Testing in the Liquor Industry, 1958 (Box GR6)
    - Canada Dry
      - Buying Incentive Study of Carbonated Beverages, 1968, (2 folders) (Box GR6)
    - Cities Service Oil Company (Citgo)
      - Citgo Diagnostic Advertising Research, 1968 (Box GR6)
    - Distillers Corporation/Seagram
      - Research Study of the Whiskey Market, 1958 (Box GR6)
      - Research Study of the Whiskey Market, 1958, (2 folders) (Box GR7)
    - Ex-Lax
      - Effectiveness of the Clock commercial, 1963 (Box GR7)
      - Effectiveness of the Construction Engineer commercial, 1965 (Box GR7)
      - Effectiveness of the Many Laughs commercial, 1969 (Box GR7)
      - Effectiveness of the School Teacher commercial, 1964 (Box GR7)
      - Effectiveness of the Single Man commercial, 1968 (Box GR7)
      - National Consumer Survey of the Laxative Market, 1964, (2 folders) (Box GR7)
    - Ford
      - Comprehension test of 1/2 Car 1/2 You print ad, 1967 (Box GR8)
      - Effectiveness of Four Service Campaign Ads, 1967 (Box GR8)
    - Formfit/Rogers
      - Progress Report on the Foundation Garment Market Target/Buyer Incentive Study, 1966 (Box GR8)
    - General Electric
      - Limited Buying Incentive Study for Porta Color, 1967 (Box GR8)
    - General Foods
      - Corporate
        - Conclusions and Implications of the Study of the Pre-Teen Market for Fun Foods, 1969 (Box GR8)
        - Pursuit of Meaningful Corporate Growth, 1970, (2 folders) (Box GR8)
      - Account Files
        - General Commercial Attribute Analysis, 1968
          - New Product Implications in the Food Field for 1972, 1967 (Box GR8)
          - Personal Care Markets Selection Criteria, 1969 (Box GR8)
          - Preliminary Studies of the Attitudes toward Cat Food, 1967 (Box GR8)
          - Report on Study for Baker's Chocolate, 1966 (Box GR8)
          - Study of the Market for Low/Reduced Calorie Products, 1968 (Box GR8)
          - Trend Study of D-Zerta Awareness and Usage 1966-1967, 1967 (Box GR8)
        - Jell-O
          - Buying Incentive Study of Packaged Snack Foods, 1968, (2 folders) (Box GR9)
        - Kool-Aid
          - Attitude and Use Study for Repositioning Twist, 1968 (Box GR9)
          - Buying Incentive Study of Powdered Soft Drinks, 1968 (Box GR9)
          - Market Segmentation Study on Dieting and Weight Control, 1970 (Box GR9)
          - Scoop on Weight Control, 1969 (Box GR9)
        - Maxwell House Division
          - Buyer Incentive Study of the Coffee Market, undated, (1 of 2 folders) (Box GR9)
          - Buyer Incentive Study of the Coffee Market, undated, (2 of 2 folders) (Box GR10)
          - Buyer Incentive Study--Divisional Implications, undated (Box GR10)
          - Buying Incentive Study--Ground Coffee Market, 1968 (Box GR10)
          - Buying Incentive Study--Implications for Maxwell House, 1969, (2 folders) (Box GR10)
          - Buying Incentive Study--Implications for Yuban, 1969 (Box GR10)
          - Buying Incentive Study--Instant Coffee Market, 1968 (Box GR10)
          - Buying Incentive Study--Yuban Implications, undated (Box GR11)
          - Instant Yuban F-R Revised Copy Test, 1968 (Box GR11)
          - Maxwell House seminar, 1971 (Box GR11)
          - Progress Report on Market Target/Buying Incentive Study of the Coffee Market, 1968 (Box GR11)
        - Post Division
          - Buying Incentive Study of the Cat Food Market, 1968, (2 folders) (Box GR11)
          - New Product Ideas for Post Cereals, 1970, (2 folders) (Box GR11)
          - Study to Evaluate the Nutritional Dimension in Ready-to-Eat Cereals, 1971 (Box GR11)
    - Gillette
      - Buying Incentive Study of the Shampoo Market, 1971 (Box GR11)
    - Gordon's
      - Consumer Study of the Gin Market, 1971, (2 folders) (Box GR12)
      - Consumer Study of the Vodka Market, 1971, (2 folders) (Box GR12)
    - Hamilton Watch
      - Copy Research Study, 1964 (Box GR12)
    - Hammond Organ
      - Facing the Future Organ Market, 1968 (Box GR12)
    - Hanes
      - Buying Incentive Study of the Women's Hosiery Market, 1965, (2 folders) (Box GR12)
    - Howard Johnson
      - Conclusions and Implications from the National Study of the Restaurant Market, 1969 (Box GR12)
      - National Study of the Lodging Market, 1969, (2 folders) (Box GR13)
    - Hudson's Department Stores
      - Segmentation Study of Metropolitan Detroit Shoppers, 1971 (Box GR13)
    - J.C. Penney
      - Marketing presentation, 1964, (2 folders) (Box GR13)
    - Lovely Legs
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1959-1965, (2 folders) (Box GR13)
      - Print advertising, 1959-1960 (Box GR13)
      - Women's Shaving Cream Market, 1959 (Box GR13)
    - Marine Midland Bank
      - Consumer Market for Retail Banking, 1971, (3 folders) (Box GR14)
    - Mennen
      - Exploratory Study of a Baby Magic Lotion Ad, 1967 (Box GR14)
      - Sales projections, 1961 (Box GR14)
      - Second Validation of Two Sales Projection Techniques, 1962 (Box GR14)
    - P. Lorillard
      - Advertising Penetration Study on Kent Cigarettes, 1966-1968, (3 folders) (Box GR14)
      - Effectiveness of Old Gold Filter Hero Commercial, 1965 (Box GR14)
      - Implications for a New Cigarette Brand, undated (Box GR14)
      - Kent Penetration Study, 1969 (Box GR14)
      - National Study of Cigarette Usage and Brand Switching, 1967 (Box GR14)
      - Presentation of new cigarette brand concepts, 1964 (Box GR14)
      - Report on a Penetration Study for Kent Deluxe 100's, 1967 (Box GR15)
      - Report on First Wave Results of an Advertising Study on Kent, 1966 (Box GR15)
    - Procter & Gamble
      - Analysis of storyboards, 1968 (Box GR15)
      - Analysis of Top Job Humphrey Commercial, 1967 (Box GR15)
      - Buying Incentive Study of the Peanut Butter Market, 1966 (Box GR15)
      - Discussion of Market Testing for Media Evaluation, 1962 (Box GR15)
      - Year-End Sales Meeting, 1968 (Box GR15)
    - RCA Victor
      - Buying Incentive Study of the Classical Record Market, 1964 (Box GR15)
    - Revlon
      - Buying Incentive Study for Colorsilk, 1970 (Box GR15)
      - Consumer Blind Product Test of Two Revlon Hair Sprays, 1963 (Box GR15)
      - Consumer Study of the Los Angeles Lipstick Market, 1965 (Box GR15)
      - Consumer Study of the Los Angeles Lipstick Market, 1966 (Box GR16)
      - Effectiveness of Colorsilk Screen on Screen Commercial, 1967 (Box GR16)
      - Evaluation of Future Marketing/Distribution Opportunities, 1967 (Box GR16)
      - Marketing Recommendations for Revlon Hair Sprays, 1963 (Box GR16)
      - Research Study of the Hair Color Market, 1964 (Box GR16)
      - Study among Consumers of the Corporate Images of Five Cosmetics Companies, 1961 (Box GR16)
      - Study of Consumer Attitudes toward Cover Gray Hair Color, 1967 (Box GR16)
      - Study of Hair Coloring Users, 1968 (Box GR16)
      - Study of the Cosmetic Market, 1968, (1 of 3 folders) (Box GR16)
      - Study of the Cosmetic Market, 1968, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box GR17)
      - Summary Presentation for Management of the Cosmetic Consumer Study, 1968 (Box GR17)
    - Rheingold
      - Advertising strategy, 1967 (Box GR17)
      - Copy Research Study, Baseball Commercial, 1967 (Box GR17)
    - R.H. Macy
      - Study of the Potential Opportunities and Problems Facing Macy's in New Haven, 1964 (Box GR17)
    - Samsonite
      - Limited Buying Incentive Study for Samsonite Contoura Luggage, 1965 (Box GR17)
    - Sentry Insurance
      - Market study, undated, (2 folders) (Box GR17)
    - Sugardale Foods
      - Preliminary Report on an In-Use Test of Reddi Bacon, 1968 (Box GR18)
      - Reddi Bacon marketing plan, 1968 (Box GR18)
    - Tidewater Oil
      - Buying Incentive Study--Retail Gasoline, 1964-1965, (4 folders) (Box GR18)
      - Review of marketing and advertising research, 1965 (Box GR18)
      - Study of Tidewater's Marketing and Advertising, 1966 (Box GR18)
    - United Fruit
      - Final Report on the Rightaway Egg Salad Product Test, 1968 (Box GR19)
      - Study for Freeze-Dried Salads, 1965 (Box GR19)
    - Vantage House
      - Copy Pre-Testing Procedures and Recommendations, 1965 (Box GR19)
    - Wallace Silversmiths
      - Composition of the Sterling Silver Flatware Market, 1967, (2 folders) (Box GR19)
    - W.T. Grant
      - Benchmark Study of Grant's Customers and Attitudes, 1966 (Box GR19)
      - Buying Incentive Study--GM& A [General Merchandise and Apparel] Store Market, 1967 (Box GR19)
      - Effectiveness of Girlswear Easter commercial, 1966 (Box GR19)
  - General Files
    - 39 Loaves of Bread: An Analysis of the Morality of Advertising, 1967 (Box GR19)
    - Assistant Account Executive and Account Secretary, 1967 (Box GR19)
    - Attitude Shift--European trip, 1963 (Box GR20)
    - Believability, 1957 (Box GR20)
    - Changing Nature of Service Departments, 1967 (Box GR20)
    - Checkerboard, 1961-1966, (3 folders) (Box GR20)
    - Communications control, 1967 (Box GR20)
    - Copy research, 1961 (Box GR20)
    - Copy testing, 1962-1963, (2 folders) (Box GR20)
    - Copy testing criteria, 1964 and undated (Box GR21)
    - Creative Research Seminar, 1960-1969 (Box GR21)
    - Development of Marketing and Creative Strategies, 1965 (Box GR21)
    - Discussion of Market Testing for Media Evaluation, 1962 (Box GR21)
    - Early attitude material, 1959-1960 (Box GR21)
    - Evaluation of Creative Research at Grey, 1964 (Box GR21)